McKelvey, Jean T. Papers /3001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jean T. McKelvey Papers
1991-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
McKelvey, Jean T.
/3001
140.44 cubic feet
140.4 linear ft.
Administrative papers.
3069679
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 13, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Jean McKelvey (February 9, 1908 - January 5, 1998) was one of the founding faculty at the New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University in 1946, the first female member of the National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA) in 1947, the NAA's first female president in 1970, and an accomplished author of many works on arbitration and other labor topics. The first fully endowed chair at the ILR School was named the Jean McKelvey-Alice Grant Professorship of Labor-Management Relations.
A graduate of Wellesley College (AB '29, MA '31) and Radcliffe College (PhD '33), McKelvey taught at Sarah Lawrence College from 1932 to 1945. She joined the newly-formed New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations in 1946 as the school's first professor, reaching the rank of full professor in 1951. She became Professor Emerita in 1976. In addition to developing the ILR School's fields of study with Maurice Neufeld, teaching at the ILR School, and conducting scholarly research, McKelvey served on the Region II National War Labor Board (1944-1945), New York State Board of Mediation (1955-1966), the Federal Services Impasses Panel (1979-1990), and other boards and panels.
Among her many honors and awards were the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service's Special Award for Distinguished Service in Labor Management Relations (1973), Arbitrator of the Year Award from the American Arbitration Association (1983), and Distinguished Services Awards from Wellesley College (1975), the Society of Professionals in Dispute Resolution (1989), and the Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals (1990).
See the Cornell University Faculty Memorial Statement for Professor Jean McKelvey
Scope and Contents
Collection includes papers relating to her career as teacher, author, former President of National Academy of Arbitrators, member of arbitration panel of American Arbitration Association, member of New York State Board of Mediation, member of Public Review Board of United Auto Workers, member of the Special Advisory Panel to the President's Review Committee on Federal Employee-Management Relations, member of mediation, fact-finding and arbitration panels of the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, member of the Federal Service Impasses Panel and member of Emergency Boards appointed by the President under the Railway Labor Act.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4165 OHT: Jean T. McKelvey Interview with Ronald Schatz /4202: Jean T. McKelvey Additional Files /4208: Maurice F. Neufeld and Jean T. McKelvey, eds. "Industrial Relations at the Dawn of the New Millennium" Monograph 5154: New York City Office of Collective Bargaining Records
Arbitration, Industrial--United States.; Industrial arbitrators--United States.; McKelvey, Jean T. (Jean Trepp), 1908-1998.
3069679
- A-D (Box 1)
  - Aaron Benjamin, 1963-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ab-, 1953-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ac-Ad, 1951-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Comm on Automations Mon, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ah-Ai, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Air Canada, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Al-An, 1969-1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alexander, G., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Amer. Arb. Association, 1948-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Amer. Arb. Association Conf. Syracuse, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1947-1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Amer. Arb. Assn. Syracuse Conf., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Associated Press (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Amer. Fed. Of State, County - Washington, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Sterilizer, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ap-Ar, 1949-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arbitration + Int. Discipline, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration + The Courts, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Arbitrators, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arbitration Conf. - Syracuse '65, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Arbitration - General, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Arbitration - Pendry Cases, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - American Arbitration Industry, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - As-, 1962-1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Assn. of labor Mediation Agencies, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ALRA, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ba, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bea-Berm, 1948-1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bernstein, I., 1949-1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bern-Bey, 1957-1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bi-Bl, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bo, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bra-Bri, 1954-1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Broc-Brop, 1958-1973 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Browde, Sanford, 1953-1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Brown, 1954-1977 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bru-Bu, 1955-1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bur of National Affairs, 1955-1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bur of National Affairs, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bureau of National Affairs - Copyright Release, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bureau National Affairs - Manuscripts, 1952-1955 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Can- Cas, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cartoons, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cass, M., 1955-1971 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cass-Chot, 1946-1963 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Chatman, D., 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Chi-Cl., 1952-1966 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cole, David, 1952-1978 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Colem-Cons, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Collective Bargaining forum, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Cont - Con., 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Committee on Academic Women, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - CU Grievance Panel, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Cow-Cra, 1968-1977 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Cre-Cro, 1948-1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Cu, 1947-1981 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Da-Dav, 1948-1968 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Day, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - De-Di, 1948-1976 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Do, 1947-1979 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Dock Study - Corresp., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Doering, B., 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Dr-Dz, 1947-1989 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Duty of Fair Representation Conferences, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Duty of Fair Representation Conferences, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Duty of Fair Representation Conferences, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Duty of Fair Representation Conferences, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Duty of Fair Representation Conferences, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- E-L (Box 2)
  - Ea-Ed, 1978-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ei-Ev, 1951-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Fa-Fe, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Federal Mediation + Cancellation Service, 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Film Lists, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fi-Fl, 1950-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fos-Fow, 1947-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fowler-George, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fou-Fy, 1949-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ga, 1955-1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ge-Gi, 1953-1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Gl-Gol, 1951-1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gom-Gos, 1949-1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Gou-Gra, 1957-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gt Brit. Arb 71, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Greenbaum, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Greenbaum 1 of 4, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Gree-Gu, 1958-1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Groat Award, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Hac-Ham, 1947-1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Han-Har, 1948-1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Has-Het, 1951-1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Hef-Hes, 1949-1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Ho-Horr, 1956-1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Horvitz, Aawn, 1947-1955 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Horvitz, Wayne, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Hou-Hu, 1946-1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - I, 1947-1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Industrials Relations Research Assn. (IRRA), 1958-1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - IRRA - Exec. Bd. - 1957 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - IRRA - Paper - '68 - Corresp., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - IRRA - Paper - '68, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - IRRA Spring Meeting '66, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - International Society for Labor Law + Social Legislation, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Israel 1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Ives, 1957-1981 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Ja-Je, 1950-1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Lenson, V., 1946-1956 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Ji-Jo, 1951-1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Jones, Ralph Research Proposal on Impasse Proved, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Kab-Kan, 1946-1963 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Kar-Ke, 1946-1964 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Kh-Ki, 1947-1971 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Kl-Kr, 1968-1979 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Lab-Laf, 1958-1962 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Lam-Laz, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Le, 1953-1985 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Li, 1963-1977 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Ll-Lov, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Lu-Ly, 1948-1955 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- M-O (Box 3)
  - Mac-Maj, 1956-1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Mal.-Mar, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mas-May, 1949-1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Materials Requested, 1955-1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Materials Requested, 1962-1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Mca-Mcc, 1948-1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - McD-McT, 1958-1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - McKelvey - Annual Rats, 1982-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - McKelvey - Annual Rats, 1962-1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - McKelvey - Geographical, 1955-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - McKelvey - Book Reviews, 1952-1960 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - McKelvey - Penting, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - McKelvey - Personal - General, 1947-1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - McKelvey - Personal - General, 1960-1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - McKelvey - Personal - General, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - McKelvey - Personal - Library - Archives, 1977-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - McKelvey - Personal - Retirement, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - McKelvey - Speaking Engagements, 1949-1959 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - McKelvey - Speaking Engagements, 1955-1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - McKelvey - Speaking Engagements, 1960-1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - McKelvey - Speaking Engagements, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - McKelvey - Speeches - Texts, 1947-1961 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - McKelvey - Vita, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - McKersie, R., 1971-1983 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Me-Mi, 1950-1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Mineworkers Election '69, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Mo., 1946-1965 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Monwe County Grievance Committee - '69, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Moore, David (Dean), 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Mu-Max, 1948-1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - NA, 1957-1962 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Nat'l Civil Service League, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - National Workers Bd., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ne, 1955-1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - NYS Bd. Of Med., 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - NYS Off of Emp. Rel., 1973-1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Ni-No, 1947-1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - O, 1968-1983 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Ornati, Oscar, 1955-1965 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- P-Z (Box 4)
  - Pa, 1943-1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Pe-Pl, 1948-1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Placement - General, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Po, 1966-1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Portus, John, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Pr-Pu, 1947-1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ra, 1951-1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Rehmas, 1963-1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Re, 1958-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Research Projects, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ri, 1969-1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Rob, 1957-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Roc, 1956-1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Rochester (N.Y.) City, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Rog-Ros, 1965-1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Rot-Ru, 1961-1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Saat, 1945-1947 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Sab-Sa, 1961-1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Sal-Say, 1954-1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Salzburg Seminar, 1951-1958 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Seha-Sehm, 1946-1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sehn-Seg, 1951-1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Seitenberg, J., 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Seitz, P., 1954-1974 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sel-Sex, 1951-1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Sh, 1950-1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Si, 1948-1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Sl-So, 1946-1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Sp-Stan, 1974-1981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Stark, A, 1954-1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Star-Sto, 1953-1970 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Str-Stu, 1957-1965 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Su-Sz, 1967-1982 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Ta-Th, 1955-1973 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - To-Tri, 1948-1954 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Tru-Ty, 1960-1972 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - U, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor (50th Anniversary), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - U.S. Dept of State, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - V, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Wae-Wal, 1967-1983 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Willen, 1954-1967 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - War-Wein, 1946-1950 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Weis, 1949-1972 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Weisburger, June, 1930-1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Weitzman, Joan, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Weitzman, Joan, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Weitzman, Joan, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Wellesley College, 1947-1970 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Wellesley College, 1948-1953 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Wellesley College, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - McKelvey - Wellsley Coll Award '75, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - McKelvey - Wellesley Coll. Award '75, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Wel-Wes, 1954-1961 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Wh-Wile, 1950-1974 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Willcox, 1953-1964 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Will-Wir, 1946-1977 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Wit-Wor, 1948-1980 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - X, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - y, 1958-1980 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - z, 1965-1984 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Misc., 1978 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- A. General Correspondence: Arranged in alphabetical order. Includes school related and department files.; B. ILR Committee Files: Includes correspondence and memos regarding various school committee activities (Box 5)
  - Advisees - Undergrads, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Alumni - Conf. + Meetings, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary 25th - 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 50th Anniversary, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Catherwood '48-'51, 1948-1951 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Catherwood '52-'55, 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sle-, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Catherwood '57-'58, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights Course, Rochester, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - C.B.U. Lm Dept. Admin., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - C.B.U. Lm. Dept. - Meetings, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - C.B.U. Lm Dept. - Meetings, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - C.B.U. Lm Dept. - Pers Polium (some items Remove + to Restricted Bx. 141), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - C.B.U. Lm Dept. -Pub Emp., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Memorandum's, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - CB,U,Lm, Dept. - Recruitment (Some items Removed to Restricted Bx. 141), 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - CB,LL,Lm Dept. - Teaching Assignments, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Dept. of International + Comp Lab rel., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Extension - Amalgamated Course, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Extension - Amalgamated Course, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Extension (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Extension Div., 1967-1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Faculty - General, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Faculty-General, 1947-1958 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - ILR Review, 1948-1995 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - ILR Review - Arb. Research., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - ILR Review - A.G. Research, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - ILR Review - Cook Co. Fact-Finding, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Library-ILR, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - McKelvey, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Placement Information, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Public Employment Sourcebook, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Publications - ILR, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Student Papers - Corresp., 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Student Papers - Corresp., 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Advisory Council, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Committees -, 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Extension Comm., 1964 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Extension Comm., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Committees - General, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Committees - Graduate, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 5259, 1952-1959 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Committees - Graduate '60, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Committees - Graduate, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Groat Award - Award Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Groat Award, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Committees - ILR Review '62-'69, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Committees ILR Rev., 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Institute Pub. Emp. - Adv. Comm., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Committees - MILR Compose Exam, 1963-1967 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - MILR - Law Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Committees - Nominations + Elections, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- A. General Correspondence: Arranged in alphabetical order. Includes school related and department files.; B. ILR Committee Files: Includes correspondence and memos regarding various school committee activities (Box 6)
  - Committees Pers Policy '56, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Committees - Personnel Policy, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Committees (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committees - Personnel Policy '57, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Committees - Personnel Policy '58, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Committees - Pers Pol '63, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Committee - Pers Pol '69, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Comm = Pers Pol '69, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Memorandums, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Committees Pers Pol. - '70, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Pers Pol Comm. '71, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - McKelvey, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pers Pol Comm. '72-'75, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Pers Pol. Sub-Committee, 1958-1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Pers Pol. Sub-Committee, 1957-1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Committee - Res + Pubs., 1948-1961 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Res + Pubs Comm. '68, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Res. + Pub. Comm '68, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Res. + Pubs. Comm '69, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Res + Pubs Comm '69, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Res + Pubs. Comm. '69, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Res + Pubs. Comm. '70, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Committees - Symposium + Detroit '62, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Committees - Symposium + Det. '62, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Business Week (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Wallen Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Wallen Fund, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Wallen Fund 1971 Expenditures (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Wallen Fund '72, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Wallen Fund '73, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Wallen Fund '73, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Wallen Fund '74, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Wallen Fund '75-'76, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Wallen Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Wallen Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Wallen Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Wallen Fund - Brook Landis Book, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Wallen Fund - Contributors, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Wallen Fund - Masterlist, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Wallen Fund - Pending, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Wallen - Prize, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Wallen - Prize, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- C. ILR Conferences/Programs: Arranged alphabetically by title of Conference.; A (Box 7)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conference, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Air Transport Lab Rel. Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Air Transport Lab Rel. Conf., 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Air Transport Lab Rel Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conf., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conf., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Air Transport Labor Rel. Conf., 1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Air Transport Lab. Rel. Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Air Transport Lab. Rel. Conf., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Alternatives to Coll Berg., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Arb. Dev. Preg. - Admin, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Arb. Dev. Preg. - AAA Training, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Attendance (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Arb. Dev. Program - Course Materials, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. Follow up '73-'74, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Arbitrators Dev. Prog. Follow up '74-'75, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. Follow-up '73-'74 Questions I, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Follow-up '73-'74 Questions 2, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Follow-up '73-'74 Question 3, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. Follow-up Seminar Rochester, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Council '71-'73, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - General '71-'73, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Group Sessions, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Group Sessions, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. Informal Inquiries, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. Lists of Cases from Trainees, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. McDermott Rpt. (NAA Meeting), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. Meeting Agendas Announcements, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Others, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Other Programs, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- A-C (Box 8)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Participant - Alston, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Alutto, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Atlesan, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Atlesan, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part. - Croft, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Curry, 1960-1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Denson, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Doering, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog - Part - Foldman, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Foster (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Foster, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Goodman, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Goodman, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog - Part - Hoelole, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Maroney, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - McDonnell, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Noble, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Noble, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog - Part - Pastore, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Pohlman, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Port - Rinaldo, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Rinaldo, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Stevens, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog - Part - Stocker, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Arbitration, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Part - Whalen, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Participants - Misc., 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - Teaching Materials, 1967-1971 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Arb. Dev. Program - Trainees, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Arb. Dev. Prog. - vs. Dept. of Lab. Meeting '72, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Buffalo Conference 2/67, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Conference - Arb. -1957 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Conferences - Arb. - 1959 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Arbitration, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Conference - Arb. - '62, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Conferences - Arb. - Comments '54, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Conferences - Arb. - Delegates - 1954 (Box 8, Folder 38)